All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of
the Grand Line. These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World. Now,
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
Reuniting after their training, Luffy and his crew continue on to the New World.
The first stop is Fishman Island, where they find themselves pulled into a civil war.
After meeting with Jinbei, they learn of the events that led to their battle with the new
Fishman pirates. They also learn of Queen Otohime, who despite opposition, fought for understanding
between humans and fishmen.
Be careful, Mother.
Don't go, Mother!
Queen Otohime!
What? I don't get it. Where is she going?
My queen.
Trust in me. Have faith in the woman you married, and the humans.
Goodbye, Mother!
I will miss you!
Come home safe!
You have missed me!
Please be careful up there!
I love you, Mother!
A sudden tragedy! A gunshot shuts down the future!
Queen Otohime's voyage would determine the fate of Fishman Island and its people.
Of course, the uncertainty weighed heavily upon our shoulders. But for her family, it was
even worse, I'm sure.
Her children were restless, awaiting news of her safe return. In this, the island was united.
Whether we were royalty or commoners, all we could do was pray for our queen.
What? A magic box?
Yep. In the palace. It's called the tomate box, to be exact.
And it has the power to make you suddenly grow older?
Yep. Well, that's what they say at least.
So that means, if a kiddo like the princess opened it, then BAM! She'd be a full grown sexy babe lickety split?
That would be the idea, sir.
Problem solved! That is just what I need! Now I can get married to Shirahoshi right away and it won't be creepy! Or so I suspect.
Now! Go and steal that magic box thing and steal it quick! No, wait. That gate at the palace is gonna stop us for sure, huh?
I say you just marry her first and work out the details later.
Yeah, everybody knows you're a creed.
Whoa! Now there's an idea! Shirahoshi is pretty cute already. Even if the box thing doesn't work out, if I give it ten years or so, she'll be a knockout.
Yeah, but she's gonna get even bigger, you know.
Hey! Different strokes for different folks, buddy! I happen to like big women just fine!
Not to mention, she can control the Sea King so her powers are big too! As big as my ambitions!
She just needs the right man in her life! And we'll have the whole world in the palm of our hands!
That means money, money, money, money! I'm telling you it's my destiny! The dream of every decade sets the beginning of time!
Now, let's get started on writing those wedding invitations, shall we?
You have to propose to her first!
Wait! I don't have any friends!
Days passed with no word from the Queen. The hearts of her people grew heavy.
I really miss hearing her speeches.
Please return safely, Queen Otohime!
Boss? What's wrong? Why isn't she back?
You think something bad happened?
Keep the faith. She is fighting to protect your future, children. This island's future.
Our hearts are with you, Your Majesty.
Please come home!
Worry not, my children. Your mother is a strong and wise woman.
Wise woman.
Although it was but a week, it felt like an eternity.
Then, at long last...
Hm?
Finally!
She's back! Your Majesty!
I was so worried!
I'm not crying, I just have something in my eyes.
She's back!
Your Majesty!
I was so worried!
I'm not crying, I just have something in my eye!
Welcome home! Your Majesty!
After several days of negotiations, Queen Otohime was able to
quell the fury of the Celestial Dragons. And perhaps more importantly,
she brought a piece of paper back with her that would prove a beacon of hope to our entire
island. In truth, it was a greater miracle than any of us could have imagined.
Everyone, despite our troubled history with them, the Celestial Dragons
are very influential. And by meeting with them, I have been able
to bridge a gap. We may attend the World Summit
yet. Listen to what they've written to improve humankind's
relationship with fishmen. We give this petition written by
their Queen. Our full endorsement.
In other words, if we can fill my petition with
signatures, the World Leaders at the Summit
will have no choice but to recognize our
right to be there. And furthermore,
our right to be a part of the surface world.
Finally, we will see our dream!
I have mixed feelings about getting support from those guys.
I'm still not sure.
And now, it's in your hands. We still need more signatures.
I have found the way, but this is a path we must walk together.
Please, let your cry for freedom be heard.
Only then, can we live above among our human friends.
We've come so far! Please! Your signatures can change our future!
Thank you, bud. Don't get my hopes up. If you're just going to change your mind again...
We won't! My mom said she's gonna sign too!
Unh...
Toro Lunci
Ha...
No offense, Majesty, but I think you're going to need a much bigger box.
And you better hurry, because the whole country's going to be lining up.
Don't worry, Your Highness. I had a feeling this might happen.
Those of you who support our Queen, put your signatures in here, please!
There's only so much we can do by ignoring our prejudice.
We need someone like her to take a step forward.
We can denounce hate, but to instill hope is a far greater gift.
This is our future-given life, sooner than we ever imagined.
She can transform this island more than a life of fighting ever could.
I wish that Arlong understood that to save him from hatred.
I wonder, what will he think of our future?
I wish Tiger were here. Surely this would have warmed his heart.
Mother, signatures keep pouring in from all over the country!
Things seem to be progressing well.
It's a dream come true.
Yeah, and your courage made it come true!
Well, I...
did feel some inspiration.
I felt as if a new road had been paved for the future of our people,
when that miracle happened.
Miracle?
Yes.
What else could you call the appearance of those Sea Kings?
That was nuts!
Think they like us?
No.
Shirahoshi called them here.
I don't think it's so strange.
After all, we can speak to fish, can't we?
That's part of what it means to be merfolk.
And yet, whenever we try to communicate with the great Sea Kings,
for whatever reason, our words fall on deaf ears.
No one on Fishman Island can speak to whales except for your father.
But the Sea Kings, well, they're beyond even him.
They say, in a legend passed down by our family,
that every few hundred years,
a mermaid will be born into the royal house
with a fearsome power that no one else on the island possesses.
The power to talk to Sea Kings?
And Shirahoshi is the one?
I believe she is.
And according to the rest of the legend,
she will meet someone who will guide both her and her power
in a direction that will change the world.
I can't wait to see.
Oh, wow!
Of course, if the world does change,
then that will likely mean a change to this island as well.
Yeah?
You think it'll help with the world's summit thing you're doing?
Perhaps.
For if it is used with love,
her power could save thousands of lives.
That is my hope.
But who can say?
It may be darkness that will rule her heart instead.
In that case, her power could sink the world.
Of course, Shirahoshi is just a child.
I'm sure she has no such intentions.
But because she is a child,
she has yet to understand her power
and cannot control it.
If something traumatic were to happen to her,
she could unwittingly cause the Sea Kings to go berserk
and in great numbers.
What?
Then our whole island would be smashed into itty-bitty bits!
What the heck should we do?
Don't worry.
You can count on me to take care of her for the time being.
Although, one of these days,
the three of you must become warriors,
brave and true.
Then, as warriors and brothers alike,
use your strength
to protect your sister no matter what.
Yeah!
But of course!
Thank you.
But even as they made that vow,
they could not have expected what would come next.
Signatures for the petition were mounting at a rapid pace.
The islanders were still distrustful of humans.
But they longed to see the beginning of a new era all the same.
Hey, Queen Ojohime!
We signed papers again so you can have more!
That's against the rules.
Each person can only vote one time.
Ugh!
We're sorry.
It's okay.
Even if I can't accept them,
it's the thought that counts, right?
Thank you.
I mean it.
It seems her persistence is finally paying off.
Get away!
Fire!
Are we under attack?
What's going on?
Water!
Get water!
Quick!
Put it out!
Who would do such a thing?
We'll lose all of the signatures at this rate!
Hurry!
Run away!
Wait!
Your Highness, no!
It's not too late!
Save whatever you can!
You can't do this!
It's too dangerous!
I didn't make it this far just to lie down and give up!
Be careful!
I will protect them to my last breath!
These aren't just papers!
This is our future!
We can't let the future of our island go up in flames!
Yes, ma'am.
Save any papers you can!
Yes, sir!
Retreat to safety.
You can count on us.
Yes, sir!
Queen Otohime has been shot!
Someone find the shooter!
Don't let the culprit escape!
We'll help!
Guard the royal vandler!
Mother, no!
Mother!
It's too dangerous here!
Get on the gondola and quickly!
Move!
Don't go!
Your Majesty, answer me!
Who would tell this?
Otohime!
Oh, what a shame!
Well, don't mind me.
Nothing suspicious going on here.
Who are you?
No one!
Stay away from the princess!
Hey!
Stop!
Please, someone tell me she's all right!
Say something!
No!
It can't be!
Dammit!
No one do such a thing!
We need a doctor!
What's taking so long?
Oh, please!
Answer me, Mother!
Come on, open your eyes!
Whoever did this, I'll make them pay!
I'll make them pay!
Yes, I'm here, Mother!
My little angels, stay by my side.
However you feel, you must remain calm.
I let my guard down.
I was so excited about all of the signatures that I failed to protect them.
And look what happened.
Dear Fukuboshi, let me suffer this anger.
Your Majesty, we're here to operate.
Listen.
It doesn't matter who did this to me.
Don't become angry on my behalf.
I don't want that.
Don't submit to resentment.
Don't let hatred get the better of you.
In my name or any other.
If something traumatic were to happen to her, she could unwittingly cause the Sea Kings to go berserk.
Look, and in great numbers.
Again?
Sweetie, no.
Hey, Joshi, look!
I don't know what's going on.
Let's get along.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
Your brothers will be here for you.
wherever you go.
ori Brown.
Glo desenhy.
Five, six, three, four, four, four, four.
Ma-boo, mom-boo.
Shake it up high.
Shake it down low.
Ma-boo, mom-boo.
No! It's just fun, huh?
Do-re-mi-fa, this is so very fun!
How was that an object in time for this?
Where are you doing this? Get them out of here! Hurry!
Look, brother, we're happy!
We won't be here at all, just like you told us!
We will protect our little sister!
Don't you worry!
Just ask and we'll make it so that he knows!
Stop struggling!
You need to calm down and get back to the palace!
I swear to you, the signatures that burned, I will collect again!
And just like our father, your sons will become noble warriors!
With all of our strength, we will protect Shirahoshi and body and spirit alike!
So please, mother, please!
You need not worry about us!
Please, mother...
I don't know.
We are almost there. Our new home, in the light of the sun.
We are almost there.
We have plunged into uncertainty yet again.
As hope turns to resentment, the seeds of Hordi's rebellion are planted.
And yet, Fukuboshi refuses to give up.
After completing his tale, Jinbei begs for forgiveness.
Nami's response surprises him and her crew alike.
On the next, One Piece, back to the present, Hordi makes a move.
I'm going to be king of the pirates.